# Lucky Jain

# Software Engineer

Phase 2, Haripura Vidisha, MP 464001 +91 7247064715 luckyjain7247@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack web developer specializing in React js, Node js, and JavaScript. I provide effective solutions from both the frontend and the backend side. I have helped corporations further their growth by creating smooth, attractive and interactive Web Applications with my skills. I am an enthusiastic, productive, highly energetic and a skillful programmer who is always open to learn new technologies and find opportunities to grow.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS. JavaScript, React JS, Node JS, REST APIs, Bootstrap 5, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, SaSS, Git, JSON, Frontend Development, Full Stack Development

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Six30 Labs, Bangalore (KT)- SDE 1

MAY 2022- PRESENT

- Develop web applications (coding frontend and backend).
- Take on Heavy projects and collaborate with team members to build effective solutions.
- Approach and fix a wide range of issues on both backend and frontend side.
- Build a highly scalable, customizable and reusable code to help speed up the work on upcoming projects.

#### Six30 Labs, Bangalore (KT)- SDE 1 intern

FEBRUARY 2022 - MAY 2022

- Work on Real Projects and collaborate with team members.
- Learn how the complex projects are built.
- Build attractive Web designs using HTML and CSS.

#### **EDUCATION**

**St Mary's PG College, Vidisha (MP)**- B.Sc. (Computer Science)

June 2018 - September 2021.

### **PROJECTS**

# **Full Stack Blog Application**

JULY 2022

 MERN Stack application. Image upload, Login, Register, CRUD operations. Use of Context API for state management. Attractive UI using Bootstrap 5.

#### **React JS Admin Dashboard**

MAY 2022

• React + Firebase application. Image upload, Login, Register, CRUD operations. Used Firestore for Image Upload. Attractive UI using Bootstrap 5 and Material UI.

## **Google Keep Clone**

APR 2022

• MERN Stack application. Login, Register, CRUD operations. Use of Context API for state management. Attractive UI with exact theme as Google Keep, built using Bootstrap 5.